{"data":[{"question":"They have ______ a lot of whisky.","a":"drunk","b":"drank","c":"drinking","d":"drinked","answer":"1","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Drink - Drank - Drunk","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I ______ in Paris yesterday.","a":"was","b":"be","c":"went","d":"beed","answer":"1","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n - Is\/am\/are - Was\/were- Been","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ a piece of bread yesterday.","a":"eat","b":"ate","c":"eaten","d":"eating","answer":"2","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Eat - Ate - Eaten","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The children ______ late last night.","a":"came","b":"comed","c":"camed","d":"coming","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Come - Came - Come","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She arrived ______ the meeting ten minutes early.","a":"at","b":"in","c":"to","d":"-","answer":"1","explain":"- Arrive in : general location\n\n- Arrive at: specific location","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We arrived ______ London very late.","a":"on","b":"in","c":"at","d":"-","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Arrive in : general location \n- Arrive at: specific location ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"You haven't _______ the lesson properly.","a":"studied","b":"studyed","c":"studyied","d":"studid","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Study - Studied - Studied","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The little girl ______ the glass on the table","a":"puted","b":"putted","c":"puten","d":"put","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense) \n- Put - Put - Put","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I have already ______ the meat.","a":"fry","b":"fried","c":"fryed","d":"fryd","answer":"2","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Fry - Fried - Fried ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The children haven't ______ yet.","a":"come","b":"came","c":"coming","d":"comed","answer":"1","explain":"- Verb tense: Present (Present tense) - Past (Past tense)- Past Participle (Perfect tense)\n\n- Come - Came - Come","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"72","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}